tatatu.com 2018-12-24

# TaTaTu Privacy Policy - tatatu.com

Last Updated: May 4, 2018

#### 1\. Introduction

Tatatu Enterprises Ltd and its affiliates (collectively, “Tatatu”, “we”, or “us”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it in through our compliance with this policy.

PLEASE READ THIS POLICY CAREFULLY TO UNDERSTAND OUR POLICIES AND PRACTICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION AND HOW WE WILL TREAT IT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH OUR POLICIES AND PRACTICES, YOUR CHOICE IS NOT TO USE OUR WEBSITE.

When you use or access any of Tatatu’s websites, including the official website of Tatatu (https://tatatu.com) (collectively, the “Website”) and its related websites), you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

This policy may change from time to time (see Section 10, Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

Our websites may contain links to other websites which are not maintained by Tatatu. This privacy policy only applies to the web sites of Tatatu. When visiting these third party websites, you should read their privacy policies which will apply to your use of the websites.

#### 2\. Information we collect about you and how we collect it

**2.1 Collection of information**  
We may collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

• by which you may be personally identified, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“Personal Information”);  
• information that is about you but does not personally identify you, such as information about the device you use to access the website (for example, your computer or smartphone), your internet connection, the content you access on the Website, the number of times you access the Website, the amount of time you spend accessing the Website, your IP addresses, information collected through cookies, and other, similar information.

**2.2 How we collect information**  
We collect this information:

• Directly from you when you provide it to us.  
• Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

#### 3\. Information you provide to us

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

• Information that you provide when you register to use our Website, post material on our Website, or engage in transactions using our Website.  
• Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.  
• Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before carrying out a transaction through our Website.  
• You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the Website, if any, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

#### 4\. Information we collect through automatic data collection technologies

**4.1 Non-personally-identifying information**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

• Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.  
• Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.  
• Browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may include personal information, or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties.

**4.2 Data collection technologies we may use**

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

• **Cookies (or browser cookies)**. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of our website (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by our web analytics service provider, which will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  
• **Flash Cookies**. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.  
• **Web Beacons**. Pages of our the Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

#### 5\. How we use your information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:  
• To present our Website and its contents to you.  
• To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.  
• To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.  
• To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.  
• To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.  
• To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.  
• To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.  
• In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.  
• For any other purpose with your consent.

#### 6\. Disclosure of your information

From time to time, we may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

• To our subsidiaries and affiliates.  
• To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.  
• To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Tatatu’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Tatatu about our Website users is among the assets transferred.  
• To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.  
• For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.  
• With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

• To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.  
• To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.  
• If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Tatatu, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### 7\. Choices about how we use and disclose your information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

• Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.  
• We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way.

#### 8\. Third party advertisers

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

#### 10\. Your California privacy rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@tatatu.com](mailto:privacy@tatatu.com)

#### 11\. Changes to our privacy policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

#### 12\. Contact information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [privacy@tatatu.com](mailto:privacy@tatatu.com)
